arenabot.com 2018-08-27

# Privacy Policy | ARENABOT - MAKE ENDLESS PROFITS FROM CRYPTOCURRENCY TRADING

Last Revised: June 25, 2018

This Privacy Policy, as amended or otherwise changed from time to time (the “Privacy Policy”), explains the manner in which https://ArenaBot.com. collects, uses, maintains and discloses user information obtained through the Site. The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Hybrid Blockchain Solutions Inc., Las Vegas, Nevada. By using the Site, you (“User”) consent to the data practices prescribed in this Privacy Policy. On occasion, Arena Bot may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in law, our personal data collection and use practices, the features on the Site, or advances in technology. If material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, the changes will be prominently posted on the Site. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use. 

Please note: This Privacy Policy does not cover any information that we may receive about you through channels external to Arena Bot. 

**What information does Arena Bot collect?**

If you open an Account to utilize the Services, we may collect your full name, address, phone number, email address, and other similar information; date of birth; government issued identification; other personal information provided by 3rd party identity verification services; and information you provide to Arena Bot when interacting with our customer support or other staff members via email, online form, troll-box, or other correspondence. We also collect passive information which includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, referral URLs, your location, and other session data. We collect your personal information to provide the Services to you. We notify you about your account activity, process transactions, provide customer support services, improve our product, identify, prevent, and report potentially suspicious, fraudulent, or illegal activities, and we notify you about important changes to our Terms of Use.

**How does Arena Bot share my personal information?**

It may be necessary to disclose your information to comply with any law, subpoenas, court orders, or government request, defend against claims, investigate or bring legal action against illegal or suspected illegal activities, enforce our Terms of Use, or to protect the rights, safety, and security of Arena Bot, our users, or the public. Arena Bot may contain links to other 3rd party websites which are regulated by their own privacy policies. Arena Bot is not responsible for the privacy policies of these 3rd party websites even if they were accessed using the links from our site.Other than as stated in this Privacy Policy, Arena Bot does not disclose any of your personal information to third parties unless required to do so by law enforcement, court order, or in compliance with legal reporting obligations. 

**How can you update your information?**

You can update your information by contacting support and making a request.

We will retain your information for as long as your Account has not been closed or as needed to provide you access to your Account. If you wish to close your Account, open a ticket in our support center. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our Terms of Use.

**How does Arena Bot use cookies and persistent local data?**

We collect web browser Information in order to enhance your experience on the site and track how the Services are being used. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive, and in addition to using cookies to provide you with a better user experience, we use cookies to identify and prevent fraudulent activity. The information collected can include, but is not limited to, your IP address, referral URLs, the type of device you use, your operating system, the type of browser you use, geographic location, and other session data. Cookies are not permanent and will expire after a short time period of inactivity. You may opt to deactivate your cookies, but it is important to note that you may not be able to access or use some features of our site. Please note that Arena Bot is not responsible or can be held liable for any loss resulting from your decision or inability to use such features.

**What security precautions does Arena Bot take to protect me?**

We take the protection of your personal information seriously. We use industry-standard data encryption technology and have implemented restrictions related to the storage of and the ability to access your personal information. Arena Bot servers and business operations are entirely located in the United States.

Please note that no transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy as outlined above, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)].
